Thomas Doyle-Engler

Full-stack Web Developer

Personal Data

Phone:

704-817-0378

Whatsapp:

+1 607-287-5262

Email:

tpdoyle87@gmail.com

Social Media

Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/tde
Github:

www.github.com/tpdoyle87

Soft Skills

Communication
Collaboration
Problem Solving
Leadership

Hard Skills

Git
PostgreSQL
SAP

Programming Languages

Ruby

Rails

Javascript - ES6

jQuery

HTML

CSS

Webpack

React

Languages

English - Native Portuguese - Intermediate High performing web developer with a passion for making products with a great user experience. Recently prototyped a intuitive and user friendly tool for asset managers in Brazil to have better control over their day to day trading needs. I have a passion for growing my knowledge and never let a chance to learn something new slip away.

Experience

Free Lance Web Developer, Self-Employed - 2018 - Present

- Created a financial market prototype for a financial company in Brazil atlanticohub.com.
- Mentoring fellow coders to help them achieve better quality code and to talk them through issues.

Quality Assurance, Sabic, Selkirk, NY - May 2017 - June 2018

- Extensive SAP too complete COA, material movement and holds, material ordering and much more.
- SAP scripting to automate repetitive and time consuming tasks
- Escalating quality issues and discovering the root cause of the issue.
- Having weekly meetings with production and management to go over the major issues from the previous week.

Welder, Various construction Companies; Houston, TX - 2016 - 2017

- Lifetime responsibility for the quality of the welds performed inside the refineries
- Communicating to management any issues that arise while performing my duties to ensure the highest quality product.
- · Working long hours to make sure the job gets done on time

Conductor, CSX Transportation, Selkirk, NY - 2012 -2016

- Communicating with customers expected arrival times and any deviations from our schedule
- Finding solutions to mechanical issues while in between rail yards to keep us on schedule.

Education

Le Wagon - Full-stack Web Development; Rio de Janeiro - 2018

University of Phoenix — A.A. Accounting, Online — 2011 - 2013

References

Pedro Meyer - Le Wagon; Whatsapp — +33 631 454 618

Dave Demopier - Sabic, R & D Manager — 1 (518) 577-0662